[indistinct chatter]
[FEMALE STUDENT 2A]
Oh, my gosh.
There's one boy here
that I'm totally into!
Same here!
Do you mean the blonde guy?
Yeah, yeah!
He's too beautiful to be real!
Ah? That guy?
[both laughs]
[FEMALE STUDENT 2B]
For real? Where?
What a cutie!
[UKA]
Takamine. Seto. Endou.
And Miura.
They're all together.
It's so crazy.
Did all that stuff
really happen to me yesterday?
♪
[metal creaking]
I'm still doubting myself.
I need to stop!
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
Hmm.
Morning.
So nice to see you again.
♪
[Kai sighs]
[UKA]
I don't know.
Maybe it really didn't happen.
[KAI]
Speak up.
[gasps]
C'mon, try again.
-Morning!
-[all gasping]
Yeah.
Maybe scale it back?
Morning, Ishimori!
[gasps]
[UKA] Before, I started
my days with a prayer
to keep my heart
out of harm's way.
"Please let me
get through the day
as still as a stone."
But starting today,
I won't ask for that.
[Uka whimpering]
Whoa, you good?
She's kinda funny, huh?
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct chatter]
SPARKLE 2 TURNING
INTO A TREASURE
[MARIN] Keep going!
Quick, take the shot!
[SATORU]
Uh-oh.
There's that stone face
we've heard about.
Yeah, she's completely
frozen up.
[UKA] I can't move around
too much during gym class.
You are always
getting in the way!
Stay back and don't move!
[UKA] Gotta make sure
I'm not in the way.
But still,
that does look like fun.
Uh!
Now, she's pretending to play.
Does she seem okay to you?
What do you think?
-Uh?
-Huh?
-[KAI] Ayumi.
-Hm?
[AYUMI]
'Sup?
[whispering]
Hm?
Uh, are you sure?
[KAI]
Just do it.
[thumping]
What was that?
[sighs]
[ASUMI]
Over here!
-[MIKARIN] Pass the ball!
-[groaning]
[YUKINO]
Do something already!
Hmm.
[AYUMI]
Ishimori!
[gasps]
-But why her?
-Since when can she catch?
[UKA] Endou actually
passed the ball to me.
-[Uka sighs]
-You got this! Go for it!
[UKA]
Yeah, I have to try!
-[gasps]
-Wait, what?
[UKA] I didn't realize
she could play basketball!
[grunts]
[metal creaking]
-Oh!
-[gasping]
[panting]
How's that?
♪
[gasps]
Uh...I'm sorry.
[all cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
[ASUMI] You've got some
real moves, Ishimori!
[YURU]
Yeah, nice shot!
[MARIN]
That was nothing but net!
I've imagined
doing that a lot before.
♪
-How'd you know?
-Luck.
[SATORU]
No kidding?
Hey, where are you going?
Kai told me to pass to you,
but I wasn't expecting that!
-Me too.
-I was nervous.
Really didn't wanna
put you on the spot.
[AYUMI]
But, hey, I figured
Kai wouldn't say that
just to be mean.
[UKA]
Yeah.
I don't think he would, either.
[clattering]
[UKA'S DAD]
I'm impressed.
It seems like your students
are actually taking
their studies seriously.
I leave my daughter
in your capable hands.
[ABE] Very good.
There's nothing to worry about.
Thank you, Mister Ishimori.
Good day, then.
♪
[SATORU]
Yo, Ishimori.
So...why'd you
pick this school?
-Huh?
-[AYUMI] I wanna know, too!
Hmm.
Because it spoke to me.
There are things here
I've only ever dreamed of.
[AYUMI]
Like what?
The students here
are having fun.
There's a sense of freedom,
like, in a good way.
Can't argue there.
Hachimitsu's the perfect fit
if you wanna slack off a bit.
We barely ever have
to study for tests,
and our school events go
way harder than they need to!
Plus, the rules are lax.
So, how would you
wanna spend your time?
♪
I'd like to hang out
with friends after school.
Maybe try staying out
past curfew for once.
[AYUMI] We could sneak
into the school after dark!
Yeah!
[UKA]
I want to try it all!
Anything I wouldn't do before!
-[KAI] Not happening.
-[gasps]
[TOGETHER]
Huh?
Quit faking.
Do you think you're like that?
Cut the crap.
[Uka gasps]
Hey, c'mon, man.
Where's the attitude
coming from?
Lookie here!
Kai, wanna hang out?
I think I'll pass.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2B]
Such a meanie!
Come chat with us, please!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2A]
Your friends can come with,
-if you want!
-Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
[UKA]
Even if it's true,
I didn't expect
to hear it from him.
Let's go.
♪
[whimpering]
[AYUMI]
Hold up, Kai!
Don't you think you were
kinda hard on her back there?
Last I checked, you were
trying to help her, right?
She's a pain.
[AYUMI]
Is that all you have to say?
[footfall]
[machine whirring]
♪
[UKA] I can't deny
any of that, though.
It's not like my dreams
will really come true.
Even if things were
going well for a while.
I've had a lot of dreams.
I wonder...
is everyone like this?
[glass shattering]
[MIZOGUCHI]
What are you doing?
[Masashi laughs]
[MASASHI]
Shut your trap!
[indistinct chatter]
[FEMALE STUDENT 2F]
Someone call the cops!
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
[AYUMI]
What's that?
-This doesn't look good.
-Hm.
♪
[footfall]
[REMI] That's right, Ishimori's
still in the classroom.
You'll find her in 1-B.
But I never said
that I wanted you guys
to show up here at our school!
Ah? For my sake?
Yeah, that's sweet and all.
Oh, right, and that
blonde jerk's name is Miura.
No, I don't know
where he's at...
Ah?
[whimpering]
[REMI] [whimpering]
He's here!
And I think he heard
everything I said!
What are we supposed to do now?
See what I mean by a pain?
[Kai sighs]
[running footsteps]
You can say that...
but off you go
sticking your nose in.
♪
[UKA]
What do I do?
I need to get
out of here, fast.
Uh-huh!
-[MASASHI] Hello!
-[gasps]
[MASASHI] We've got a special
delivery for someone!
-Oh, Ishimori!
-[gasps]
Class 1-B's very own Ishimori!
[UKA]
Why are they looking for me?
[MASASHI] Hey!
Get the hell out here, girly!
[Masashi laughs]
[door slides open]
Where's Ishimori?
[footfall]
Bummer.
Don't tell me you're not here?
[MASASHI'S MALE FRIEND 2A]
Nah, we're not gonna
fall for that so easily.
[MASASHI]
Just a matter of time.
-[MASASHI] Come out, come out!
-[UKA] But why?
♪
[UKA] What did I do?
How did I make an enemy?
[gasps]
Unless...
Oh, no.
See you.
[Masashi's male friend
2A scoffs]
[MASASHI'S MALE FRIEND 2A] You
really suck at hide and seek.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
Come on,
don't play hard to get!
[Uka groaning]
There.
Sorry, baby.
[MASASHI]
This is for my girlfriend.
Now, let's go.
[UKA] Why does it all
have to go bad now?
[sighs]
My dreams were
starting to come true.
I can't let them end!
-[KAI] Ask someone for help.
-Hmph!
Ah?
[UKA]
But who?
-[KAI] Me.
-[UKA] Miura!
[grunts]
Ah?
♪
[gasps]
Stay back.
[rustling]
[both gasping]
[MASASHI'S MALE FRIEND 2A]
Chill out.
[both screams]
Weren't you looking for me?
[KAI] Good news.
It's your lucky day.
You found me.
Don't pull this bullshit again.
Yeah?
[panting]
Hey, Masashi!
[REMI]
Miura's coming here...
[Remi gasps]
[both whimpering]
[MASASHI] You never said
he was the type
to start throwing stuff!
I never said you should
come here in the first place!
[MASASHI]
No, I remember you told me--
[MIZOGUCHI]
Hey!
Oh, we gotta run!
[MIZOGUCHI]
Stop right there!
I'll have you expelled!
[REMI]
No, please!
[sighing]
Ah!
[whimpering]
♪
[UKA]
Ah?
♪
[KAI] [chuckles]
Good timing.
Your dad would've fainted
if he had seen that.
-But he took off.
-Huh?
[UKA]
He was here? Why?
[KAI]
He's worried about you.
Now, go home.
[UKA]
Was that why... Earlier...
I put the thought in your head.
I'll follow through.
[KAI] Do you realize
how silly your dreams are?
They're small.
I'll make them all come true.
[gasps]
[KAI]
So...
keep your ass out of trouble
for your dad's sake!
[whimpering]
-And go home early from now on!
-Ah! Right!
[groans]
And such a pain.
[whimpering]
♪
[UKA]
He protected me.
And scolded me.
Hold on, this is too much!
I need to process
everything that's happened.
I need time!
♪
Back then, I barely dreamt.
I couldn't chase them,
so why bother?
♪
But now, things are different.
I want to make
my dreams reality.
[wind whooshing]
I can.
He makes it feel possible.
♪
Which can only mean one thing.
Even though
I've never experienced
this feeling before?
[gasps]
I know...
when I look at Miura,
it's love.
♪
[footfall]
I don't have social skills.
I don't even have friends.
Romance is foreign to me.
I had never
considered it before.
[exhales]
[grunts]
[groans]
But I can't deny it.
There's someone I like, now.
[MIZOGUCHI]
This'll be on the test,
so commit it to memory.
If you can't do that,
at least write it down.
And, Miura?
Wake up!
[KAI]
Ah? Was I asleep?
More like "comatose."
[MIZOGUCHI] If only I could
be your age again.
You don't know
how good you have it.
Living without a care
in your heart,
or a thought in your head.
[UKA]
No, you're wrong.
Miura's the most thoughtful guy
I've ever met.
He pays attention
to the people around him,
and he knows what they'll do.
Plus, he's always super honest
about what he thinks.
Actually, if I'm being honest,
I don't even know him
well enough
to talk about him like that.
[indistinct chatter]
Wow, nice earrings!
[chuckles]
Thanks, they're new!
[UKA]
Oh, those are cute.
They look great.
Seriously!
[gasps]
[SATORU]
Where'd you get them?
[UKA]
Hold on, she's blushing.
-[UKA] Does she like him?
-Wanna go today? -Today?
[UKA] They could be dating,
for all I know.
Yeah, sure.
[UKA] But watching them,
even I can tell
they have good chemistry.
Wow.
♪
I wonder how he really sees me.
From that look?
A pain in the neck.
[SATORU]
Yo, Kai.
[UKA]
Anyway...
I need to focus on making sure
I don't screw
things up for him.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA] I'm just happy I get
to breathe the same air as him.
-That's enough.
-So kinda like it, or whatever.
-[KAI] Huh?
-[AYUMI] Hm?
Where'd she go?
[AYUMI]
Maybe she went home?
♪
[footfall]
Huh!
I have to wonder.
Do others see me
the same way I do?
Is that Ishimori?
Oh, whoa.
Yep, that is her!
-Who is she?
-It's "Stony," the dweeb.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2H]
Oh, yeah!
Woof, that uniform
does not look good.
[MALE COLLEGE STUDENT 2A]
Who's the nerdy chick?
-New friend of yours?
-Ew, seriously?
Just some girl that went
to junior high with us.
Oh?
Well, see ya later.
[all laugh]
[UKA] Miura said that stuff
back then for my protection.
But still...even
if I know that,
it hurt.
[TOMOYA]
Sorry about that.
It seems we got here
a little bit late.
You're too late for what?
[groaning]
[UKA]
Uh-oh.
Is he mad at me
for some reason?
Now you go home earlier?
C'mon!
You said...
I think Kai really wanted
to hang out with you
after school.
-That right?
-Yeah?
Remember what I said.
About your dreams?
[UKA]
You meant it?
I thought you were joking!
Like I'd joke about that!
-You're such a pain.
-[gasps]
[KAI]
Come on, let's get going.
[UKA] [whimpering]
This is amazing.
I can't believe it.
I'm so happy!
♪
But...I'm confused.
Isn't he embarrassed to be
seen out in public with me?
-[sighs]
-[KAI] Yo, Stony.
Huh?
-Uh, that's not--
-Huh?
-Speak up!
-Oh.
-I, just--
-I can't hear you!
Now, now!
First things first.
What time is your curfew?
[UKA]
Oh, uh...
It's 5 o'clock.
[KAI]
Um?
Forget it,
we'll do it some other time!
[UKA]
Hey, I'm sorry, but--
[KAI] I keep telling you
to stop apologizing!
[UKA]
It's just that I'm so sorr--
-So what?
-Sorghum!
-That supposed to be funny?
-[UKA] No, I--
Why in hell would you yell,
"Sorghum?"
[UKA]
I wish I knew!
[KAI]
You're the one who said it!
-[Tomoya groans]
-[UKA] I know.
-So?
-[Tomoya chuckles]
-I swear!
-[Tomoya laughs]
[TOMOYA]
Sorry.
Right now,
it's just kinda hard to tell
if you two get along at all.
You really shouldn't be
worried about it, Ishimori.
He's the one who's being
awkward at the moment.
He usually
doesn't talk to girls.
[UKA]
Huh?
Yeah, and now you see why.
[sighs]
[UKA] You know, he said
something yesterday.
He mentioned
following through with me.
If I get all weird
and stony again,
I'd be getting
in his way even more.
Gotta pull myself together.
[TOMOYA] What do you think?
Shall we walk you home?
No, I'll be all right.
Really!
Ah, I mean,
aren't you on your
way somewhere?
We're both off to karaoke.
Got a few folks waiting on us.
[UKA]
Karaoke?
Listen, would it be okay
if I walked with you,
just to the entrance?
[KAI] Dunno.
Where's your place?
That way.
Just past
the pedestrian bridge.
Ah?
Well, I can walk you that far.
Huh?
[chuckles]
Yeah, go.
I'll stay right here.
[footfall]
[traffic humming]
[UKA]
I'm actually walking with him.
♪
Thank you.
I said, "Thank you, Kai!"
I heard you the first time.
I just wanted you to know
that I really mean it.
Tell me, what do you really
think about yourself?
[gasps]
Me?
That I'm still like a stone.
Are you ever gonna make up
your mind for good?
Decide on being one way,
or the other?
♪
[KAI]
Might as well just be a stone.
[gasps]
Well, what else are you hiding?
"Hiding?"
[KAI] Like how you're
not really bad at sports.
Uh, that just kinda happened.
Just think about it.
How much you could do
if you tried.
[KAI] There are
probably a lot of things.
♪
I mean, yeah,
I talked to you that night.
That was just the springboard.
You're the one
who took it from there
and actually made the jump.
Don't keep letting your
old self drag you down.
♪
Be a stone.
But be a gemstone.
[gasps]
♪
[KAI]
You can want more.
Be a little greedy.
And as for everybody
who gave you a hard time?
Know that you're
better than them.
Now...
you're taking your
first steps to happiness.
♪
[UKA] I always
hated that nickname.
But he turned it into
something...precious.
Hey, now I have a new dream.
[UKA] It may not
come true soon, but...
You won't see me
as a pain ever again.
Uh?
♪
If someone was watching us now,
they would think I was
just a bully making you cry.
[gasps]
I'm--
Sorghum?
-[UKA] Ah!
-[laughs]
I don't even know what that is.
[laughs]
♪
It's okay.
Do whatever you want.
-[UKA] See you tomorrow.
-[KAI] Great.
♪
[sighs]
Hmm.
[panting]
[UKA] I'm better than the
people who bullied me before.
I deserve better!
♪
It's already starting.
I'm listening
to all the things he says
and taking the first steps
to happiness.
I don't think I'll ever meet
someone like him again.
[crying]
Not for as long as I live.
♪
I'm not sure that
I'm even good enough
to fall in love with him,
but oh, well!
'Cause there's
no turning back now!
♪
[TOMOYA]
Hm?
Seems like she'd do
whatever you asked her to.
Well, she was lost before.
Once I set her straight,
she got weirdly attached to me.
[Tomoya chuckles]
No one else even noticed
she existed.
Hm?
So, it was easy
to rock her world.
All it took was you
talking to her a bit.
[TOMOYA]
There are worse things.
And honestly?
I think she's pretty cute.
[sighs]
Hah, of course,
I'm the kinda guy
that thinks all girls are cute.
Hmm.
♪
[UKA]
I have a new dream.
To get confident enough
in myself...
so that I can tell Miura...
I'm in love with him.
That's what I have to do.
TO BE CONTINUED